Guide to the Administrative Papers of Chancellor George Bugliarello RG.007
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series VII: Correspondence, 4406
  - Lawrence Chiarelli – "Dream Team Recruits", 2010 August; 5457 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Porter Cogeshall – Naval Forces Review, 2010 September; 5458 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Jack Day - University of Wisconsin – Green Bay, 2010 December - 2011 February; 5459 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Earth Systems Engineering, 2002 August; 5460 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Dr. Andrey E. Egorov – St. Petersburg State Architectural and Civil Engineering University, 2005 April-November; 5461 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Fred Eirich, 2003 July; 5462 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Dr. Masoud Ghandehari, 2010 October-November; 5463 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Daniel Goodman – RESTRICT, 2005 August-September; 5464 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Richard E. Hanley – RESTRICT, 2005, 2007; 5465 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Hofstra University, 2010 February; 5466 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Barbara Kates-Garnick, 2009 September - 2010 May; 5467 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Barbara Kates-Garnick, 2009 June-September; 5468 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Dr. Melissa Knothe Tate – RESTRICT, 2010-2011; 5469 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - William A. Kuperman, 2005 January; 5470 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Dato Lee Yee-Cheong – World Federation of Engineering Organizations, 2003 June - 2004 November; 5471 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Gene Luntey, 2001 June 9; 5472 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Tony Marjoram – UNESCO, 2004 March-May; 5473 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Dr. Hans Mark, 1998-2004; 5474 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Peter A. Mckenzie – Cobos, Ellington, Maduabum & Mckenzie LLC, 2010 April; 5475 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Megacities Project - Janice Perlman, 2001 June - 2002 December; 5476 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970-1983, 5599 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985-1997, 5600 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975-1992, 5477 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous, 1993, 1993 June-November; 5478 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous, 1994, 1994 June-July; 5479 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous, 1997, 1997 July-December; 5480 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous, 2009-2010, 2009 December, 2010 September; 5481 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous, 2010, 2010 April; 5482 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous, undated, 5601 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Bala Mulloth – Reference Letter – RESTRICT, 2011 January; 5483 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Dr. Norman P. Neureiter, 2010 December 17; 5484 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Dr. Norman P. Neureiter – Indo-US Science & Technology Forum, 2010 May-June; 5485 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - Diya Obeid, 2003 May; 5486 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Janka Ovcharovichova – Harrisburg Area Community College, 2010 September; 5487 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - Dr. Baldev Raj – Sustainable Cities, 2010 July-September; 5488 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Elizabeth Dianne Rekov – "The New Frontiers in Engineering Design" Symposium, 2008-2010; 5489 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Andrew W. Reynolds – Deputy Science and Technology Adviser to the Secretary of State, 2004 March-April; 5490 (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - Adolph Rodriguez, 2002 March 8; 5491 (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Subrata Saha – 6th International Conference on Ethical Issues in Biomedical Engineering, 2010 May - 2011 March; 5492 (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - Subrata Saha – Ethics in Biology, Engineering & Medicine an International Journal, 2009-2010; 5493 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - Subrata Saha – Ethics in Biology, Engineering & Medicine an International Journal, 2011; 5494 (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - George Schillinger, 2008 December - 2009 December; 5495 (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - Pasquale M. Sforza, 2005 February; 5496 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Harold P. Sjursen – History and Philosophy of Science and Technology Program, 2007 August; 5497 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - George Smith, 1999 November; 5498 (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Dr. Subra Suresh, 2010 October; 5499 (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - University of Manitoba – Dr. Richard Gordon, 2010 August, October; 5500 (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Richard Wener, 2005 February; 5501 (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - Debora Wince-Smith, 2005 January; 5502 (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - Walter B. Wriston, 1995 September 18; 5503 (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Siro Polo Padolecchia (last descendent of Marco Polo) - Correspondence (Oversize), 2007-2008; 4452 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Series VIII: Photographs & Slides, 5688
  This series contains photographs ranging from 4"x6" to 8"x10" which include formal portraits, images of George Bugliarello attending University events, a series of photographs of MetroTech construction and a series of photographs of a Russian delegation visit to the Polytechnic campus. The slides depict MetroTech construction, text, and figures used by George Bugliarello for presentations.
  - Subseries A: MetroTech Construction, 5690; 3"x 5" color prints
    - Miscellaneous, Undated; 2308 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Jay Street, 1990; 2309 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Groundbreaking, 1990 April 19; 2310 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Moving Historic Houses – Construction, 1990 March; 2311 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous– Construction, Undated; 2312 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - MetroTech Commons, Undated; 2313 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Renaissance Plaza, 1983-1998; 2314 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn Union Gas, 1990; 2315 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Chase, 1991 October; 2316 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - S.I.A.C. – Construction, 1988 March; 2317 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Construction, 1988-1993; 2318 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Metrotech and Related Photos, undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: U.S.I., 5691; 3"x 5" color prints
    - Russian Delegation Visit – Academy of Sciences Anti-terrorism Task Force – 1, 2005; 2456 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Russian Delegation Visit – Academy of Sciences Anti-terrorism Task Force – 2, 2005; 2457 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Russian Delegation Visit – Academy of Sciences Anti-terrorism Task Force – 3, 2005; 2458 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Subseries C: George Bugliarello, 5692; 3" x 5" to 8" x 10" black and white and color prints.
    - Miscellaneous, Undated; 5693 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Headshots, 2001; 5694 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Posed, Undated; 5695 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Posed, 1989 January; 5696 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - MetroTech, 1989; 5697 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Negatives, 1982, Undated; 5698 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Headshots, circa 1973-2011; 5699 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Events - Miscellaneous, Undated; 5700 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Mayor Ed Koch, Mayor's Commission for Science and Technology, 1990; 5701 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Mayor Ed Koch, 1989; 5702 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - U.N. Ambassadors, Undated; 5703 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Seminar - I.C.E., Undated; 5704 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Meeting in Bern Dibner Library, 1993 August; 5705 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Luncheon, 1993 October 18; 5706 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Event – Miscellaneous, 1990 February 21; 5707 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Female Speaker (Unknown), Undated; 5708 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Gruman Hall, circa 1976; 5709 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Commencements, undated; 6481 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Subseries D: University Relations, circa 1973-2011; 5713
    Provenance
    The following folders were transferred from the University Development Office photo collection (H11-074).
    - Photo File - 1, circa 1973-2011; 5714 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Photo File - 2, circa 1973-2011; 5715 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Photo File - 3, circa 1973-2011; 5716 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Photo File - 4, circa 1973-2011; 5717 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Subseries E: Slides, Undated; 5712; 35mm slides in 2" x 2" mounts. (Box 54)
    Scope and Content
    This box contains miscellaneous containers of labeled and un-labeled slides of images of MetroTech construction and various presentations given by George Bugliarello on university and urban development.
  - Subseries F: Miscellaneous
    - Polytechnic University Long Island Center, undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Poster/Comic Strip (Learning Aid?), undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Oversized slides, Poly statistics, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Series IX: Ephemera, 5689
  This series contains a collection of business cards and name tags collected by George Bugliarello. The name tag collection, which was transferred from George Bugliarello's home, represents nearly forty years of George Bugliarello's academic and professional activities.
  - Business Cards, 5711 (Box 57, Box 55)
  - Nametags, 5710 (Box 56)
  - George Bugliarello Memorial Day in Brooklyn certificate. Office of the President, Borough of Brooklyn, City of New York., April 27, 2011; 5810 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Metrotech Hard Hat, December 12, 1990 (Box 57)
  - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, March 6, 2001 (Box 57)
- Series X: Hard drive, 1998-2011; 5719; (2.56 GB, 6,663 files, 222 folders)
  The contents of George Bugliarello's hard drive from the Chancellor's Office, Jacobs Building (Room 350) were transferred to the archives in January 2011 and are retained on a dedicated archives server. The hard drive contains 2.56GB of data in 6,663 files. These digital files have not been reorganized or altered from their original state.
- Series XI: 2022 Accretion, 1996-2005
  Scope and Contents
  These items are a 2022 accretion to the Administrative Papers of Chancellor George Bugliarello and consist of publications written or edited by Bugliarello. These items had been pulled from the collection and set aside as possible duplicates. Upon closer inspection, unique items were identified, resulting in this accretion. The accretion is located on bay 33, shelf 6E.
  - East-West Technology Transfer: New Perspectives and Human Resources edited by George Bugliarello, et al., 1996 (Box 59, Item 1)
  - Intellectual Property and Global Markets: An East-West Dialogue edited by George Bugliarello, et al., 1999 (Box 59, Item 2)
  - A Report for the National Institute of Standards and Technology reviewed by George Bugliarello, et al., 2002 (Box 59, Item 3)
  - A Biosoma Precis in Knowledge Economics: Emerging Principles, Practices and Policies by George Bugliarello, 2005 (Box 59, Item 4)